Facilities Management Department fonds
Simon Fraser University Archives and Records Management Department
- General office files, 1963 - 1984; F-11-1; 7.68 m of textual records
  - Cafeterias, 1968 - 1978; F-11-1-28; 10 cm of textual records
    - Central Mall Cafe (36-04), 1968 - 1974; F-11-1-28-0-6 (Archival box - standard 11-25)
    - Cafes - General (70-01), 1976 - 1978; F-11-1-28-0-7 (Archival box - standard 11-59)
    - East Concourse Cafe (70-02), 1977 - 1978; F-11-1-28-0-8 (Archival box - standard 11-59)
    - South Court Lounge (70-05), 1976 - 1977; F-11-1-28-0-9 (Archival box - standard 11-59)
  - Central mall, 1965 - 1975; F-11-1-29; 6 cm of textual records
    - Expenditures (Central Mall) (38-02), 1967 - 1972; F-11-1-29-0-1 (Archival box - standard 11-25)
    - Roof - General (38-06), 1967 - 1975; F-11-1-29-0-2 (Archival box - standard 11-25)
    - Breakage Patterns - CM Roof (38-06-26), 1969; F-11-1-29-0-3 (Archival box - standard 11-25)
    - Faculty Lounge (36-08), F-11-1-29-0-4 (Archival box - standard 11-25)
    - Steps and Treads (38-08), 1968 - 1975; F-11-1-29-0-5 (Archival box - standard 11-25)
    - Change Orders - CM (38-16), 1965 - 1969; F-11-1-29-0-6 (Archival box - standard 11-25)
  - Classroom complex, phase III, 1969 - 1972; F-11-1-30; 1 cm of textual records
    Imperial Construction Ltd
  - Classroom block, phase II, 1972 - 1976; F-11-1-31; 8 cm of textual records
    - Classroom Block Phase II - Bulk Excavation and Site Drainage, 1975; F-11-1-31-0-1 (Archival box - standard 11-26)
    - Classroom Block Phase II - General (41-01), 1972 - 1975; F-11-1-31-0-2 (Archival box - standard 11-26)
    - Site Survey and Soils Report for Phase II - Science Classroom Block (41-03), 1974; F-11-1-31-0-3 (Archival box - standard 11-26)
    - Classroom Block Phase II - Cost Estimates (41-05), 1975; F-11-1-31-0-4 (Archival box - standard 11-26)
    - Soils Investigation for Phase IV - Science Complex, 1976; F-11-1-31-0-5 (Archival box - standard 11-26)
    - Classroom Block Phase II - Construction Management Services (41-08), 1975; F-11-1-31-0-6 (Archival box - standard 11-26)
  - Day care centre, 1972 - 1978; F-11-1-32; 19 cm of textual records
    Daycare Centre
    - Day Care Centre - General (45-01), 1972 - 1975; F-11-1-32-0-1 (Archival box - standard 11-26)
    - Day Care Centre - Client/Architect Agreement (45-02), 1975; F-11-1-32-0-2 (Archival box - standard 11-26)
    - Day Care Centre - Site Survey and Soils Report 45-03), 1975; F-11-1-32-0-3 (Archival box - standard 11-26)
    - Day Care Centre - Testing Reports (45-13), 1975; F-11-1-32-0-4 (Archival box - standard 11-26)
    - Day Care Centre - General Part A (42-01), 1975 - 1978; F-11-1-32-0-5 (Archival box - standard 11-47)
    - Day Care Centre - General Part B (42-01), 1975 - 1978; F-11-1-32-0-6 (Archival box - standard 11-47)
    - General #2 (42-01), 1978; F-11-1-32-0-7 (Archival box - standard 11-47)
    - Client/Architect Agreement (42-02), 1976; F-11-1-32-0-8 (Archival box - standard 11-47)
    - Progress Certificates (42-05), 1975 - 1977; F-11-1-32-0-9 (Archival box - standard 11-47)
    - Miscellaneous Expenditures (42-06), 1977; F-11-1-32-0-10 (Archival box - standard 11-47)
    - Equipment and Furnishings (42-07), 1976 - 1977; F-11-1-32-0-11 (Archival box - standard 11-48)
    - Change Order Correspondence (42-09), 1975 - 1976; F-11-1-32-0-12 (Archival box - standard 11-48)
    - Change Orders (42-10), 1976 - 1977; F-11-1-32-0-13 (Archival box - standard 11-48)
    - Testing Reports (42-13), 1976; F-11-1-32-0-14 (Archival box - standard 11-48)
    - Shop Drawings (42-11), 1976 - 1977; F-11-1-32-0-15 (Archival box - standard 11-48)
    - Progress Reports (42-12), 1976 - 1977; F-11-1-32-0-16 (Archival box - standard 11-48)
    - Site Meetings (42-14), 1976; F-11-1-32-0-17 (Archival box - standard 11-48)
    - Mechanical Systems (42-15), 1976 - 1977; F-11-1-32-0-18 (Archival box - standard 11-48)
    - Electrical Systems (42-16), 1976 - 1977; F-11-1-32-0-19 (Archival box - standard 11-48)
    - Landscaping (42-17), 1976 - 1978; F-11-1-32-0-20 (Archival box - standard 11-48)
    - Deficiencies (42-18), 1976 - 1978; F-11-1-32-0-21 (Archival box - standard 11-48)
    - Fence (42-19), 1977; F-11-1-32-0-22 (Archival box - standard 11-48)
    - Warranties and Guarantees (42-20), 1976 - 1978; F-11-1-32-0-23 (Archival box - standard 11-48)
  - Gymnasium, 1968 - 1979; F-11-1-33; 5 cm of textual records
    Athletic and Recreational Services
    - Gym - General (46-01), 1968 - 1972; F-11-1-33-0-1 (Archival box - standard 11-27)
    - Bleachers - Gym (46-16), 1970; F-11-1-33-0-2 (Archival box - standard 11-27)
    - Gymnasium - General (46-01), 1976 - 1978; F-11-1-33-0-3 (Archival box - standard 11-49)
    - Kinesiology Lab (46-02), 1975 - 1978; F-11-1-33-0-4 (Archival box - standard 11-49)
    - Athletics and Recreational Services (46-03), 1975 - 1978; F-11-1-33-0-5 (Archival box - standard 11-49)
    - Renovations - Existing Gym (46-04), 1976; F-11-1-33-0-6 (Archival box - standard 11-49)
    - Swimming Pool Upgrading (46-05), 1978; F-11-1-33-0-7 (Archival box - standard 11-49)
    - Proturf Floor (47-25), 1972 - 1979; F-11-1-33-0-8 (Archival box - standard 11-49)
  - Gymnasium expansion, 1971 - 1978; F-11-1-34; 38 cm of textual records
    - Program Stage (47), 1971 - 1973; F-11-1-34-0-1 (Archival box - standard 11-27)
    - Contract Document Stage (47), 1973; F-11-1-34-0-2 (Archival box - standard 11-27)
    - General (47-01), F-11-1-34-0-3 (Archival box - standard 11-27)
    - Client-Architect Agreement (47-02), 1973; F-11-1-34-0-4 (Archival box - standard 11-27)
    - Gym Expansion (47-04), 1973; F-11-1-34-0-5 (Archival box - standard 11-27)
    - Cost Estimates (47-05), 1973; F-11-1-34-0-6 (Archival box - standard 11-27)
    - Change Order Correspondence Part 1 (47-07), 1973 - 1975; F-11-1-34-0-7 (Archival box - standard 11-27)
    - Change Order Correspondence Part 2 (47-07), 1973 - 1975; F-11-1-34-0-8 (Archival box - standard 11-27)
    - Change Orders (47-07-01), 1973 - 1975; F-11-1-34-0-9 (Archival box - standard 11-27)
    - Design Changes (47-07-02), 1974 - 1975; F-11-1-34-0-10 (Archival box - standard 11-27)
    - Program to Architects, 1973; F-11-1-34-0-11 (Archival box - standard 11-28)
    - Tenders Received (47-13-01), 1973; F-11-1-34-0-12 (Archival box - standard 11-28)
    - Inspections and Testing (47-15), 1973 - 1975; F-11-1-34-0-13 (Archival box - standard 11-28)
    - Materials Testing Reports (47-15-01), 1973 - 1975; F-11-1-34-0-14 (Archival box - standard 11-28)
    - Minutes of Site Meetings (47-16-01), 1973 - 1975; F-11-1-34-0-15 (Archival box - standard 11-28)
    - Mechanical Systems (47-18), 1973 - 1975; F-11-1-34-0-16 (Archival box - standard 11-28)
    - Electrical Systems (47-20), 1973 - 1975; F-11-1-34-0-17 (Archival box - standard 11-28)
    - Hardware (47-22), 1973 - 1974; F-11-1-34-0-18 (Archival box - standard 11-28)
    - Squash and Handball Courts (47-23), 1974; F-11-1-34-0-19 (Archival box - standard 11-28)
    - Substantial Completion (47-28), 1975; F-11-1-34-0-20 (Archival box - standard 11-28)
    - Gym Expansion - General (48-01), 1975 - 1978; F-11-1-34-0-21 (Archival box - standard 11-49)
    - Client/Architect Agreement (48-02), 1972; F-11-1-34-0-22 (Archival box - standard 11-49)
    - Progress Certificates (48-06-01), 1976 - 1977; F-11-1-34-0-23 (Archival box - standard 11-49)
    - Change Order Correspondence (48-07), 1976 - 1978; F-11-1-34-0-24 (Archival box - standard 11-49)
    - Change Orders (48-07-01), 1976 - 1977; F-11-1-34-0-25 (Archival box - standard 11-49)
    - Design Changes (48-07-02), 1976 - 1978; F-11-1-34-0-26 (Archival box - standard 11-49)
    - Inspections and Testing (48-15), F-11-1-34-0-27 (Archival box - standard 11-50)
    - Mechanical Systems (48-18), 1977 - 1978; F-11-1-34-0-28 (Archival box - standard 11-50)
    - Electrical Systems (48-20), 1976 - 1978; F-11-1-34-0-29 (Archival box - standard 11-50)
    - Renovations to Central Core (48-21), 1976; F-11-1-34-0-30 (Archival box - standard 11-50)
    - Hardware (48-22), 1976; F-11-1-34-0-31 (Archival box - standard 11-50)
    - Squash and Handball Courts (48-23), 1976 - 1978; F-11-1-34-0-32 (Archival box - standard 11-50)
    - Proturf Floor (48-25), 1976 - 1978; F-11-1-34-0-33 (Archival box - standard 11-50)
    - Classroom Complex Warranties and Guarantees (48-27), 1976 - 1977; F-11-1-34-0-34 (Archival box - standard 11-50)
    - Substantial Completion and Deficiencies #1 Part A (48-28), 1975 - 1977; F-11-1-34-0-35 (Archival box - standard 11-50)
    - Substantial Completion and Deficiencies #1 Part B (48-28), 1975 - 1977; F-11-1-34-0-36 (Archival box - standard 11-50)
    - Substantial Completion and Deficiencies #2 (48-28), 1976 - 1978; F-11-1-34-0-37 (Archival box - standard 11-50)
    - Combatives Room (48-29), 1976 - 1978; F-11-1-34-0-38 (Archival box - standard 11-50)
    - Bleachers (48-30), 1976 - 1978; F-11-1-34-0-39 (Archival box - standard 11-50)
    - Gym Outdoor Games Area (48-31), 1976 - 1978; F-11-1-34-0-40 (Archival box - standard 11-51)
    - Physiotherapy Room Renovations (48-32), 1976 - 1978; F-11-1-34-0-41 (Archival box - standard 11-51)
    - Women's Locker Room renovations (48-33), 1976 - 1978; F-11-1-34-0-42 (Archival box - standard 11-51)
    - Sound System (48-34), 1978; F-11-1-34-0-43 (Archival box - standard 11-51)
  - Library, 1968 - 1978; F-11-1-35; 17 cm of textual records
    University Library
    - Oil Storage Tanks and HPHW Mains (Library Bldg.) (50-06), 1968 - 1970; F-11-1-35-0-1 (Archival box - standard 11-28)
    - Leaks and Roof (Library Bldg.) (50-10), 1970 - 1975; F-11-1-35-0-2 (Archival box - standard 11-28)
    - Library - General (52-01), 1976 - 1978; F-11-1-35-0-3 (Archival box - standard 11-55)
    - Fire Exits (52-02), 1978; F-11-1-35-0-4 (Archival box - standard 11-55)
    - Audio/Visual Ventilation Correspondence (52-03), vol. 1, 1975 - 1976; F-11-1-35-0-5 (Archival box - standard 11-55)
    - Audio/Visual Ventilation Correspondence (52-03), vol. 2, 1977; F-11-1-35-0-6 (Archival box - standard 11-55)
    - Audio/Visual Ventilation Correspondence (52-03), vol. 3, 1978; F-11-1-35-0-7 (Archival box - standard 11-56)
    - Renovations - 1st Floor (52-04), 1977 - 1978; F-11-1-35-0-8 (Archival box - standard 11-56)
    - [Library Addition - Form of Tender Specs], 1977; F-11-1-35-0-9 (Archival box - standard 11-56)
    - Library Ventilation (52-05), 1977 - 1978; F-11-1-35-0-10 (Archival box - standard 11-56)
    - Price Contract (52-06), 1974; F-11-1-35-0-11 (Archival box - standard 11-56)
    - Library Entrance Correspondence #1 (52-07), 1977; F-11-1-35-0-12 (Archival box - standard 11-56)
    - Library Entrance Correspondence #2 (52-07), 1978; F-11-1-35-0-13 (Archival box - standard 11-56)
  - Library expansion, 1968 - 1978; F-11-1-36; 26 cm of textual records
    - Library Expansion - General (51), 1968 - 1975; F-11-1-36-0-1 (Archival box - standard 11-28)
    - Mechanical Systems (51-08), 1974 - 1975; F-11-1-36-0-2 (Archival box - standard 11-29)
    - Programme Stage (51-09), 1971 - 1973; F-11-1-36-0-3 (Archival box - standard 11-29)
    - Tenders (51-12), 1975; F-11-1-36-0-4 (Archival box - standard 11-29)
    - Change Orders (51-13), 1975; F-11-1-36-0-5 (Archival box - standard 11-29)
    - Change Order Correspondence (51-14), 1975; F-11-1-36-0-6 (Archival box - standard 11-29)
    - Electrical Systems (51-20), 1975; F-11-1-36-0-7 (Archival box - standard 11-29)
    - Library - 7th Floor Completion (51-25), 1975 - 1976; F-11-1-36-0-8 (Archival box - standard 11-29)
    - Library Expansion - General (54-01), 1974 - 1978; F-11-1-36-0-9 (Archival box - standard 11-56)
    - Furnishings (54-02), 1976 - 1978; F-11-1-36-0-10 (Archival box - standard 11-56)
    - Cost Estimates (54-03), 1976 - 1978; F-11-1-36-0-11 (Archival box - standard 11-57)
    - Progress Certificate (7th Floor) (54-06-01), 1975 - 1976; F-11-1-36-0-12 (Archival box - standard 11-57)
    - Client/Architect Agreement (54-10), 1974; F-11-1-36-0-13 (Archival box - standard 11-57)
    - Contract Documents (54-11), 1976 - 1977; F-11-1-36-0-14 (Archival box - standard 11-57)
    - Change Orders (54-13), 1975 - 1977; F-11-1-36-0-15 (Archival box - standard 11-57)
    - Change Order Correspondence (54-14), 1976 - 1977; F-11-1-36-0-16 (Archival box - standard 11-57)
    - Inspection and Testing (54-15), 1976 - 1977; F-11-1-36-0-17 (Archival box - standard 11-57)
    - Construction Progress (54-16), 1976; F-11-1-36-0-18 (Archival box - standard 11-57)
    - Minutes of Site Meetings (54-17), 1975 - 1976; F-11-1-36-0-19 (Archival box - standard 11-57)
    - Mechanical Systems #5 Boiler and Chimneys (54-18), 1975 - 1978; F-11-1-36-0-20 (Archival box - standard 11-57)
    - Electrical Systems (54-20), 1976 - 1978; F-11-1-36-0-21 (Archival box - standard 11-57)
    - Alterations and Moves (54-22), 1976 - 1978; F-11-1-36-0-22 (Archival box - standard 11-57)
    - Library - 7th Floor Completion (54-23), 1975 - 1978; F-11-1-36-0-23 (Archival box - standard 11-57)
    - Space Usage (54-23-01), 1976; F-11-1-36-0-24 (Archival box - standard 11-57)
    - Library Roof Leaks (54-24), 1975 - 1978; F-11-1-36-0-25 (Archival box - standard 11-58)
    - Library Roof Leaks #2 (54-24), 1978; F-11-1-36-0-26 (Archival box - standard 11-58)
    - Renovations and Alterations (54-26), 1976 - 1978; F-11-1-36-0-27 (Archival box - standard 11-58)
    - Kinesiology (54-28), 1977; F-11-1-36-0-28 (Archival box - standard 11-58)
  - Physical Plant and Central Stores building, 1969 - 1972; F-11-1-37; 6 cm of textual records
    - Physical Plant and Central Stores Building - General Part 1 (54-01), 1969 - 1972; F-11-1-37-0-1 (Archival box - standard 11-29)
    - Physical Plant and Central Stores Building - General Part 2 (54-01), 1969 - 1972; F-11-1-37-0-2 (Archival box - standard 11-29)
    - Central Stores and Receiving (PP and P Bldg.) (54-02), 1969; F-11-1-37-0-3 (Archival box - standard 11-29)
    - Minutes of [Site] Meetings (PP and P Bldg.) (54-04), 1970 - 1972; F-11-1-37-0-4 (Archival box - standard 11-29)
    - Contract Docs and Specs (PP and P Bldg.) (54-14), 1971; F-11-1-37-0-5 (Archival box - standard 11-29)
    - Materials Testing Services (PP and P Bldg.) (54-16), 1971 - 1972; F-11-1-37-0-6 (Archival box - standard 11-29)
    - Electrical (PP and P Bldg.) (54-18), 1971 - 1972; F-11-1-37-0-7 (Archival box - standard 11-30)
  - Playfields, 1968 - 1978; F-11-1-38; 15 cm of textual records
    - Playfields #1 to #4 (56-02), 1968 - 1975; F-11-1-38-0-1 (Archival box - standard 11-30)
    - Playfields #5 (56-04), 1969 - 1975; F-11-1-38-0-2 (Archival box - standard 11-30)
    - Playfields - Lawsuit (56-16), 1973 - 1974; F-11-1-38-0-3 (Archival box - standard 11-30)
    - Playfields - General (78-01), 1976 - 1978; F-11-1-38-0-4 (Archival box - standard 11-59)
    - Reconstruction of Playfields and Track (78-02), 1972 - 1978; F-11-1-38-0-5 (Archival box - standard 11-60)
    - General (78-02-01), 1978; F-11-1-38-0-6 (Archival box - standard 11-60)
    - Change Order Correspondence (78-02-06), 1978; F-11-1-38-0-7 (Archival box - standard 11-60)
    - Minutes of Site Meetings (78-02-08-01), 1978; F-11-1-38-0-8 (Archival box - standard 11-60)
    - Electrical Systems (78-02-10), 1978; F-11-1-38-0-9 (Archival box - standard 11-60)
    - Inspections and Testing (78-02-11), 1978; F-11-1-38-0-10 (Archival box - standard 11-60)
    - Client/Architect Agreement (78-02-12), 1978; F-11-1-38-0-11 (Archival box - standard 11-60)
    - Cost Estimates (78-02-13), 1978; F-11-1-38-0-12 (Archival box - standard 11-60)
    - Construction Documents (78-02-15), 1978; F-11-1-38-0-13 (Archival box - standard 11-60)
  - Professional Development Centre, 1968 - 1973; F-11-1-39; 3 cm of textual records
    Professional Development Centre
    - Professional Development Centre (IMS) - General (58-01), 1968 - 1973; F-11-1-39-0-1 (Archival box - standard 11-30)
    - Professional Development Centre - Expansion (58-16), 1971 - 1972; F-11-1-39-0-2 (Archival box - standard 11-30)
  - Recreational arena, 1969 - 1973; F-11-1-40; 3 cm of textual records
    - Recreational Arena - General Part 1 (60-01), 1969 - 1973; F-11-1-40-0-1 (Archival box - standard 11-30)
    - Recreational Arena - General Part 2 (60-01), 1969 - 1973; F-11-1-40-0-2 (Archival box - standard 11-30)
  - Residences - general, 1967 - 1974; F-11-1-41; 7 cm of textual records
    - Residences - General (62-01), 1967 - 1974; F-11-1-41-0-1 (Archival box - standard 11-30)
    - Water Damages - Residences (62-06), 1970 - 1974; F-11-1-41-0-2 (Archival box - standard 11-31)
    - Men's Residence - General (64), 1967 - 1973; F-11-1-41-0-3 (Archival box - standard 11-31)
    - Women's Residence - General (65), 1968 - 1970; F-11-1-41-0-4 (Archival box - standard 11-31)
    - President's Residence - General (66), 1968 - 1974; F-11-1-41-0-5 (Archival box - standard 11-31)
  - Marrried students' residence, 1967 - 1974; F-11-1-42; 11 cm of textual records
    - General (67), 1968 - 1974; F-11-1-42-0-1 (Archival box - standard 11-31)
    - Bidding and Competition (67-07), 1967 - 1973; F-11-1-42-0-2 (Archival box - standard 11-31)
    - Materials Testing (67-10), F-11-1-42-0-3 (Archival box - standard 11-31)
    - Insurance (67-24), 1968 - 1970; F-11-1-42-0-4 (Archival box - standard 11-31)
    - Electrical, Mechanical and Plumbing - General (67-26), 1968 - 1974; F-11-1-42-0-5 (Archival box - standard 11-31)
    - Extension of West Campus Mains (67-30), 1968; F-11-1-42-0-6 (Archival box - standard 11-31)
    - Transformer Failure (67-48), 1969 - 1970; F-11-1-42-0-7 (Archival box - standard 11-32)
    - Heating System (67-49), F-11-1-42-0-8 (Archival box - standard 11-32)
  - Family residences, 1969 - 1976; F-11-1-43; 8 cm of textual records
    - General (68-01), 1969 - 1972; F-11-1-43-0-1 (Archival box - standard 11-32)
    - Student Housing (68-01), 1973 - 1976; F-11-1-43-0-2 (Archival box - standard 11-32)
    - Residence Site Services (68-06), 1974; F-11-1-43-0-3 (Archival box - standard 11-32)
    - Soil Report (68-10), 1973; F-11-1-43-0-4 (Archival box - standard 11-32)
    - Baxter Proposal (68-12), 1973; F-11-1-43-0-5 (Archival box - standard 11-32)
    - Negren Study (68-14), 1973 - 1976; F-11-1-43-0-6 (Archival box - standard 11-32)
  - Science complex phase III, 1967 - 1973; F-11-1-44; 19 cm of textual records
    - Science Complex Phase III - General (78-01), F-11-1-44-0-1 (Archival box - standard 11-32)
    - Payments to Architects (78-02-03), 1970 - 1973; F-11-1-44-0-2 (Archival box - small 11-33)
    - Change Orders Part 1 (78-06), 1969 - 1970; F-11-1-44-0-3 (Archival box - small 11-33)
    - Change Orders Part 2 (78-06), 1969 - 1970; F-11-1-44-0-4 (Archival box - small 11-33)
    - Renovations, Revisions, Modifications (78-16), 1967 - 1972; F-11-1-44-0-5 (Archival box - small 11-33)
    - Electrical, Power and Heating (78-24), 1968 - 1970; F-11-1-44-0-6 (Archival box - standard 11-34)
    - Physics Department (Fume Hoods) (78-34), 1969 - 1972; F-11-1-44-0-7 (Archival box - standard 11-34)
    - Arbitration (78-58), 1969; F-11-1-44-0-8 (Archival box - standard 11-34)
    - Continental Steel and Scaffold vs. Dillingham Corp. (78-58-02), 1970; F-11-1-44-0-9 (Archival box - standard 11-34)
    - Toxic, Gases, Sealing of Windows (78-62), 1969 - 1971; F-11-1-44-0-10 (Archival box - standard 11-34)
    - Arbitration - Concrete Finishing (78-88-01), 1970; F-11-1-44-0-11 (Archival box - standard 11-34)
  - Science complex phase IV, 1965 - 1980; F-11-1-45; 48 cm of textual records
    - Science Complex Phase IV Part A - General (80-01), 1969 - 1975; F-11-1-45-0-1 (Archival box - standard 11-34)
    - Science Complex Phase IV Part B - General (80-01), 1969 - 1975; F-11-1-45-0-2 (Archival box - standard 11-34)
    - Equipment Lists and Layouts (80-03), 1975; F-11-1-45-0-3 (Archival box - standard 11-34)
    - Programme Stage (80-06), 1975; F-11-1-45-0-4 (Archival box - standard 11-34)
    - Animal Care Unit (80-08), 1976; F-11-1-45-0-5 (Archival box - standard 11-34)
    - Schematic Stage (80-09), 1975; F-11-1-45-0-6 (Archival box - standard 11-34)
    - Soil Test and Inspection (50-02), 1976; F-11-1-45-0-7 (Archival box - standard 11-51)
    - Site Investigation, 1965; F-11-1-45-0-8 (Archival box - standard 11-51)
    - Capital Expenditures (50-03), 1976 - 1978; F-11-1-45-0-9 (Archival box - standard 11-51)
    - Payments to Architects (50-03-01), 1976 - 1978; F-11-1-45-0-10 (Archival box - standard 11-52)
    - Payments to Architects #2 Part A (50-03-01), 1977 - 1978; F-11-1-45-0-11 (Archival box - standard 11-52)
    - Payments to Architects #2 Part B (50-03-01), 1977 - 1978; F-11-1-45-0-12 (Archival box - standard 11-52)
    - Miscellaneous Expenditures (50-03-04), 1977 - 1978; F-11-1-45-0-13 (Archival box - standard 11-52)
    - Fees (50-04), 1976 - 1978; F-11-1-45-0-14 (Archival box - standard 11-52)
    - Programme Stage (50-06), F-11-1-45-0-15 (Archival box - standard 11-52)
    - Plans and Specs (50-07), 1976 - 1978; F-11-1-45-0-16 (Archival box - standard 11-52)
    - Change Order Correspondence (50-08), 1976; F-11-1-45-0-17 (Archival box - standard 11-52)
    - Design Changes (50-08-02), 1978; F-11-1-45-0-18 (Archival box - standard 11-52)
    - Shop Drawings (50-08-03), 1976; F-11-1-45-0-19 (Archival box - standard 11-52)
    - Schematic Stage (50-09), 1975 - 1978; F-11-1-45-0-20 (Archival box - standard 11-52)
    - Site Investigation: Proposed Sewer, 1969; F-11-1-45-0-21 (Archival box - standard 11-52)
    - Working Drawings Stage Part A (50-10), 1976 - 1978; F-11-1-45-0-22 (Archival box - standard 11-53)
    - Working Drawings Stage Part B (50-10), 1976 - 1978; F-11-1-45-0-23 (Archival box - standard 11-53)
    - Working Drawings Stage #2 Part A (50-10), 1977 - 1978; F-11-1-45-0-24 (Archival box - standard 11-53)
    - Working Drawings Stage #2 Part B (50-10), 1977 - 1978; F-11-1-45-0-25 (Archival box - standard 11-53)
    - Teaching and Lab and Working Drawings Stage #3 (50-10), 1978; F-11-1-45-0-26 (Archival box - standard 11-53)
    - Contract Documents Stage (50-11), 1978; F-11-1-45-0-27 (Archival box - standard 11-53)
    - Construction Progress Reports (50-12), 1978; F-11-1-45-0-28 (Archival box - standard 11-53)
    - Minutes of Site Meetings (50-12-01), 1976 - 1978; F-11-1-45-0-29 (Archival box - standard 11-53)
    - Mechanical Systems (50-13), 1976 - 1978; F-11-1-45-0-30 (Archival box - standard 11-53)
    - Electrical Systems (50-14), 1977 - 1978; F-11-1-45-0-31 (Archival box - standard 11-53)
    - Hardware (50-15), 1978; F-11-1-45-0-32 (Archival box - standard 11-53)
    - Inspections and Testing (50-16), 1976; F-11-1-45-0-33 (Archival box - standard 11-53)
    - Client/Architect Agreement (50-17), 1977 - 1980; F-11-1-45-0-34 (Archival box - standard 11-53)
    - Environmental Chambers #2 (50-18), 1975 - 1978; F-11-1-45-0-35 (Archival box - standard 11-53)
    - Environmental Chambers (50-18), 1975 - 1978; F-11-1-45-0-36 (Archival box - standard 11-54)
    - Bio-Sciences Stores (50-19), 1974 - 1978; F-11-1-45-0-37 (Archival box - standard 11-54)
    - Outdoor Storage Area (50-21), 1974 - 1978; F-11-1-45-0-38 (Archival box - standard 11-54)
    - Dean of Sciences Offices (50-24), 1976 - 1978; F-11-1-45-0-39 (Archival box - standard 11-54)
    - Landscaping (50-25), 1977 - 1978; F-11-1-45-0-40 (Archival box - standard 11-54)
    - Excavation Permit (50-26), 1978; F-11-1-45-0-41 (Archival box - standard 11-54)
    - Elevators (50-27), 1978; F-11-1-45-0-42 (Archival box - standard 11-54)
    - Cana Construction Co. Ltd. Correspondence, 1978 - 1980; F-11-1-45-0-43 (Archival box - standard 11-54)
    - Cana Construction Co. Ltd. Vs. SFU - Claim, 1979; F-11-1-45-0-44 (Archival box - standard 11-54)
    - Architectural and Structural Specs Volume 1, F-11-1-45-0-45 (Archival box - standard 11-55)